[Music]
i love
my home life however i've never
considered the four walls in my one room
to be the limit of my home this valley
is just as much my living space
as my little cottage and when the
weather warms
and the spring breezes shiver the new
growth of bunch grass
my world expands no longer out of my
reach due to winter storms
it is a vast wilderness that is as
endless as it
is varied
this week i wish to share a couple
places that are close to my heart
my home away from home if you will
firstly it's this forest
a secret location that i go to in order
to collect supplies for my art projects
i come here since it is untouched by
other humans
and therefore by using proper foraging
techniques
the continuous abundance of nature is
preserved
[Music]
this wood is thoroughly enchanted in my
opinion and if you wandered through the
trees until twilight
no doubt you'd spy the dryads and fawns
dancing in the shadows
and whispering secrets to those who
listen
whatsoever enters this forest succumbs
to the otherworldly atmosphere
the white-tailed deer which are normally
quite skittish
are unafraid our shared respect for one
another perhaps
creates that harmony
[Music]
as you have no doubt noticed the
sprinkle of white on the forest floor is
due to one of my favorite flowers
it is known as the spring beauty the
first to peek through the melting snow
as early as march a gentle harbinger of
the season
of new life
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
so
my home hosts a large variety of wild
growing plants
and whenever i find something i can use
or appreciate i'm ecstatic
it is easy to go through your days
without noticing these plants
but when your soul is observant and
curious suddenly they're everywhere
as a connoisseur of herbal teas and all
their unusual and wild forms
today i decided to look for wild growing
mint and mullen for future
experimentation
while the mullen took a little stroll to
find i found the mint almost
immediately all i had to do was follow
my nose
the scent is just about the most
satisfying i know
my quest for mullen finally achieved i
found myself next to the lake
my other favorite place in my home there
are a few sounds in which i find more
contentment than the soft lapping of the
lake against the bank
i like to come here often and sit and
watch
it is incredible how nature has the
ability to remind you of what's real
in your life what is tactile not only
what you can touch
but feel
so
foreign
[Music]
do
i hope you enjoyed this video my dear
brother and i worked hard on this one
and we enjoyed the process very much
sending my love
[Music]
you